PAULINE P. NARVAS

Leeds, UK | pauline@paulinenarvas.com | linkedin.com/in/pnarvas | paulinenarvas.com

PROFILE

Equipped with a wide skill set built from various experiences, including 2 years on a competitive graduate scheme, 3 years as a remote web developer and 4 years developing technical communities. Keen in creating impactful contributions in my next role using my strong technical and communication skills. With self-development at the centre of my character, I recently became AWS Certified and have been listed in CFG's Top 25 under 30, Northern Women Power's Future List and J.P. Morgan's x The Tab Future 100 List.

EXPERIENCE

Digital Engineering Graduate

BT | Sept 2018 - Present

Two year graduate scheme, four six month rotations within BT Consumer Digital.

Rotation 3 - Platform Services | Sept 2019 - present

- Contributed in continuous improvement of our current tech focusing heavily on automation and standardising our delivery pipeline for cloud infrastructure provisioning and development CI/CD workflows.
- Assisted in helping the other engineering teams when using our CI/CD services
- Advocating Platform Services and the power of our tools to speed up releases into production
- Tech includes: AWS, HashiCorp: Terraform, Packer, Vault, Consul, Linux, Python, Ansible, k8s, Docker, Jenkins, Unix

Key achievements: Implementing Single Sign On (SSO) for Slack with Jenkins and Shibboleth for BT Enterprise and Engineering. Also, automating a self-serve website service that allows colleagues to spin up their own static website in minutes using AWS Route 53, S3 and Jenkins.

Rotation 2 - MyEE Web (Development) | March 2019 - Sept 2019

- Worked with remote developers in Belarus and India, using the Scrum approach
- Contributed to several scheduled, production releases for MyEE
- Developed Proof of Concepts that improved our current approach on automation and looked at ways to improve our current tech stack
- Tech includes: HTML, CSS/SCSS, Javascript, Java, JSP, git

Key achievements: Built new UI features on the self-serve part of the EE website, including contributing to the Roaming and Add-ons page. Also led in prioritising technical debt through refactoring project.

Rotation 1 - Digital Architecture | Sept 2018 - March 2019

- Worked with key stakeholders in the early stages of the delivery cycle to gather key requirements of propositions
- Produced impact assessments to present at the Digital IA forum
- Reviewed design documents
- Identified ways we can improve our digital tools, technology and architecture

Key achievement: Part of the team that looked at simplifying tooling strategy to better our ways of working leading to the implementation of Slack in Digital.

Other notable contributions:

- Represented BT in the Beyond Limits campaign and rebrand
- Featured in The Yorkshire Post, The Daily Mirror, The Sheffield Star to share my story
- Engaging colleagues in our Leeds office to celebrate International Women's Day and organising an event that brought together people from the local community

Working with Leeds Library to help bring digital inclusion training and awareness

Remote Web Developer

The University of Sheffield | Nov 2017 - Present

- Developed an independent research focused website for PhD students and research fellows in the Department of Civil and Structural Engineering.
- Continuous improvement with new features, site optimisation and general maintenance of the website that continues to engage researchers internationally.

Key achievement: implemented a blogging platform for research fellows can share their research and contributions in the field.

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

- 2016 2019: Organiser, Ambassador and Lead Instructor, Code First: Girls
- 2017 2018: Enterprise Intern, The University of Sheffield Enterprise (USE)
- 2017 2018: HackMed Hackathon Organiser, MedTech Sheffield
- 2016 2017: Communications and External Engagement Assistant Intern, The University of Sheffield

SKILLS & QUALIFICATIONS

- Amazon Web Services Qualified: AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner (CCP)
- Web Development: HTML, CSS/SASS, Javascript, jquery, React, Nextjs, PHP, Wordpress
- DevOps: Jenkins, Terraform, Packer, Ansible, Python, Docker
- Engagement optimisation: building online presence on social media, improving SEO
- **Confident public speaker:** Most notably as a keynote speaker at GitHub Field Day 2017 and expert speaker at "Grow from Your STEM" Gov event 2018.
- Passionate community builder: brought together different tech communities and leading various Women in Tech initiatives.

EDUCATION

The University of Sheffield | 2014 - 2018

BSc (Hons) Biomedical Sciences with Employment Experience

Tapton School | 2008 - 2014

3 A Levels: Biology, Chemistry and Sociology 12 A*-C GCSEs including Maths, English and Triple Science

REFERENCES

Available upon request